[Music]
ICICI Fox, India's leading private sector non-life insurance company, has launched 14 new and
advanced insurance products. This
includes riders for health, travel and corporate sectors. The company
announced this at a press conference in Patna on Tuesday. The
company has introduced a wide range of products across different categories
for a wide spectrum of its customers. The
company says
that the set of new products will transform the
way consumers experience insurance
and provide them with a seamless and tech-
enabled solution. Speaking
about the expansion of ICICI Fox's product portfolio,
Sanjeev Mishra, Executive Director, ICICI Fox, said, "
At ICICI Fox, we have always been at the forefront of providing
simple and cutting-edge risk
solutions to millions of customers, keeping in mind their specific needs."
He said, "Innovation is
a part of our innovative DNA.
Our comprehensive offering is
designed to meet the myriad needs of customers, irrespective of age, geography,
socio-economic background or gender."
He
said, "We are happy to announce
that we have a product for almost every segment
and inspired by the reforms made by the regulator,
we have accelerated
our efforts to develop and launch new products.
Where you have vehicles in your name, there is
a renewal document, there is a one-time premium
payment, okay, and we have a management system for insuring these vehicles together. This will actually cater to
your need in
case of any emergency. Can you
get insurance for all your vehicles in a single document?
This could be your two-
wheeler, two-wheeler,
four-wheeler, or a
combination of two-wheeler and four-wheeler. We do
n't have such a policy. Whatever private
car or two-wheeler you have, they can be covered under one policy."
[Music]
They
specifically discussed and
explained in detail the key features of the new products introduced by the company, which mainly include Golden Shield
Health, Advance Booster,
Motor Floater Insurance,
Telematics, Aid
Protect Club, Royal Home Insurance,
etc. They briefed the press in detail.
[Music]
[Music] It's been
very clearly
established that what will happen is, like,
I stole your identity, your Aadhaar problem,
through your digital footprints,
we even copied your signature,
and then we took a loan from the bank in your name.
Now, you didn't take that loan, nor did you
prepare yourself in such a way that you could take it.
What happens as a result? Your ID bounces,
your credit score gets affected.
So, in that case, if
someone sets up your identity and
creates a financial liability for you, then as a
result,
if you get any benchmarking of that,
you can find something here that
helps you get an informed decision. So,
this is an all-in-one tech
care app that has been downloaded over 2.4 million times. It allows
users to buy policies, manage claims, and
renew them on a single platform.
All this also provides convenience to the customers.
Bihar is a very large state in terms of population,
but if you look at the current situation,
we are not in a very good position in the insurance sector. So, right
now, we all
together and on this  We are working to make
Bihar better and how we are getting
activities done through awareness programs, we are getting roads constructed,
distributing helmets,
going to schools in villages and
installing purifiers,
we have started many activities
and all the companies are working together on this,
we have also included all the general insurance companies that are working in Bihar in this campaign
so that we can get organized
and take Jindal Insurance forward in Bihar
[Music]
If you liked this news then do
not forget to subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon
[Music]